[
    {
        "front": "ばしょ",
        "back": "場所 \nplace",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうじょう",
        "back": "工場 \nfactory",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろば",
        "back": "広場 \nplaza",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たてもの",
        "back": "建物 \nbuilding",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんせつ",
        "back": "建設 \nbuilding construction",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たてる",
        "back": "建てる \nto build",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たてもの",
        "back": "建物 \nbuilding",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぶつ",
        "back": "動物 \nanimal",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "にもつ",
        "back": "荷物 \nbag",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "もの",
        "back": "物 \nthings",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "びょういん",
        "back": "病院 \nhospital",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "にゅういん",
        "back": "入院 \nbe hospitalized",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいいん",
        "back": "退院 \ndischarge",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがくいん",
        "back": "大学院 \nmasters",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいがかん",
        "back": "映画館 \nmovie theatre",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいしかん",
        "back": "大使館 \nembassy",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょかん",
        "back": "旅館 \njapanese style inn",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "びじゅつかん",
        "back": "美術館 \nart gallery / museum",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくどう",
        "back": "食堂 \ndining room, canteen",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうどう",
        "back": "講堂 \nlecture hall",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうしつ",
        "back": "教室 \nclassroom",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいぎしつ",
        "back": "会議室 \nmeeting room",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "まちあいしつ",
        "back": "待合室 \nwaiting room",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "じむしつ",
        "back": "事務室 \noffice room",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうじょう",
        "back": "工場 \nfactory",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうぎょう",
        "back": "工業 \nmanufacturing  industry",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうじ",
        "back": "工事 \nconstruction",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうさく",
        "back": "工作 \nhandicraft",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ず",
        "back": "図 \nfigure  (circle, square)",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちず",
        "back": "地図 \nmap",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "としょかん",
        "back": "図書館 \nlibrary",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "あいず",
        "back": "合図 \nsign (gesture), signal",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんごう",
        "back": "信号 \ntraffic signal",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんわばんごう",
        "back": "電話番号 \nphone number",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "３ごうしつ",
        "back": "３号室 \nroom number 3",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごうしつ",
        "back": "号室 \nroom number",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごうれい",
        "back": "号令 \ncommand",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    }
]